Contact

agnesmaneomalatsi@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/agnes-malatsi-2a4584231 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Database Administration Mainframe Support Analysts

Languages

English (Full Professional)
Sotho, Southern (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

IBM COBOL Core

Cybersecurity Fundamentals Introduction to Cybersecurity IBM COBOL Data and File Management

Hands-on Introduction to Linux Commands and Shell Scripting

Maneo Malatsi

Cybersecurity | Information Security | Information Systems | Cobol Mainframe | Database Administration

City of Johannesburg, Gauteng, South Africa

Summary

I am a dedicated and emerging professional in the IT industry, currently residing in Johannesburg, Gauteng, South Africa. With a solid foundation in Information Technology, I have accumulated valuable experience in various roles, showcasing my versatility and commitment to growth in the tech space.

Experience

CAPACITI

Cobol Developer Trainee
October 2024 - Present (8 months)

City of Johannesburg, Gauteng, South Africa

Department of Basic Education Information Systems Intern August 2022 - September 2024 (2 years 2 months) Bloemfontein, Free State, South Africa

Botshabelo Digital Hub Software Development Intern April 2022 - July 2022 (4 months)

Botshabelo, Free State

Central University of Technology, Free State Student Assistant February 2020 - February 2022 (2 years 1 month) Bloemfontein, Free State, South Africa

Education

Central University of Technology, Free State Diploma, Information Technology (2017 - 2021)

Central University of Technology, Free State
Advanced Diploma, Information Technology · (2022 - 2023)